disability-benefits-help.org 2019-05-29

# Privacy Policy | Social Security Disability Help

**Privacy Policy**

**Our Commitment To Privacy**

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. 

**The Information We Collect:**

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the Disability Benefits Help website. On some pages, you can complete a free, online evaluation to be contacted by a disability attorney or advocate regarding your claim. The types of personal information collected on these pages are: 

  * Name
  * Address
  * Email address
  * Phone number(s)
  * Date of Birth
  * Case Description
  * General Information about your disability claim.

We also collect other information that does not, on its own, permit association with any specific individual. We may use this information to assist in administering the site, to learn about user behavior on the website, and to understand and analyze trends. Examples of this type of information include: 

  * Browser and device information
  * Server log file information
  * Information collected through cookies, pixel tags, and other technologies
  * Aggregated information

If we combine non-personal information with personal information, the combined information will be treated as personal information while it remains combined. 

**The Way We Use Information:**

We use the information provided when completing an evaluation to assist with a potential legal claim. We share this information with attorneys or advocates so that they can evaluate the needs of the claimant. There is no cost for this evaluation. 

We or third parties may use the information provided to contact the claimant with tips about his/her case, in addition to sending newsletters and offers for products or services. The information provided may also be used to facilitate and conduct market research or for other survey purposes. 

We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to learn more about visitors to our website. For example, we may find out that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals. 

We may be required – by law, legal process, litigation, and/or requests from public and governmental authorities – to disclose information provided on the website. 

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. 

We may collect data about your activities on our websites, such as the pages you have viewed, and may share this information with third-party companies to display relevant ads. These third-party companies may track your online activities over time by collecting information through automated means and may use this information for ad targeting. These companies typically use a cookie, web beacon, or other similar tracking technologies to collect this information.

To learn more about Internet-Based Advertising or to opt out of this type of advertising, you can visit the [ Network Advertising Alliance (NAI)](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/#!/) or the [ Digital Advertising Alliance (DAA)](http://optout.aboutads.info/#!/).

**Our Commitment To Data Security**

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

Despite these safeguards, no website, database, or system is completely secure or "hacker proof,” so we recommend that you take additional measures to protect yourself and your information, including by ensuring that you have enabled the latest security features on your devices, closing browsers after use, and installing up-to-date anti-virus software.

 **Our Commitment To Children's Privacy:**

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13. 

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums. We, or our third-party service providers, may also utilize cookies or other tracking technologies to collect information about your interaction with our website. You can disable cookies by updating the preferences in your web browser. 

A Note on Google Analytics - To help facilitate the delivery and development of relevant content, we may use Google Analytics Display Advertising, specifically the Demographics and Interest Reporting feature. You can learn more about Google Analytics Advertising and opt out [here](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/2700409?hl=en). You can view currently available Google Analytics opt-outs [here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/).

**Retention of Personal Information**

We will retain personal information for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy and for as long as we have a legitimate business purpose to do so, unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law. 

**Access to Personal Information**

To access, correct, or delete requests that are submitted on the site, please contact us using the information in the “How to Contact Us” section. 

You may have additional rights pursuant to your local laws applicable to data processing. For example, if the processing of your personal information is subject to the EU General Data Protection Regulation (“GDPR”) and your personal information is processed based on legitimate interests, you have the right to object to the processing on grounds relating to your specific situation and to object to direct marketing. Under GDPR, you may also have the right to have your personal information deleted or restricted and to ask for the portability of your personal information. For purposes of GDPR, the controller of your personal information is eGenerationMarketing, Inc. (contact details listed below), unless indicated otherwise. 

We may decline to process requests that jeopardize the privacy of others, are extremely impractical, frivolous, and/or if we are not required by local law to do so. 

**Your California Privacy Rights**

California law permits residents of California to opt out of our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. You may opt out of the sharing of your personal information with third parties by submitting a request in writing or by emailing us. 

California law also permits residents of California to request and to obtain from us once per year a list of third parties (if any) to whom we have disclosed personal information for their direct marketing purposes in the prior calendar year, as well as the type of personal information that was disclosed. There is no charge for this. 

If you are a California resident and wish to submit such a request, please contact us using the information in the “How to Contact Us” section. Be sure to include the phrase “Your California Privacy Rights” in the email subject line or on the mailing envelope, as well as your name, street address, city, state, and zip code. 

**Changes**

We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy and our related business practices at any time by updating the text on this site. If any change to this Privacy Policy affects the way we use personal information, you will be provided with a method to opt out. 

**How To Contact Us**

To remove yourself from our contact list and to unsubscribe, please visit: http://www.disability-benefits-help.org/form/unsubscribe 

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies or would like to make a privacy-related complaint, please use our Privacy Contact Form. 

You may also contact us via mail: 

326 A Street - Unit 1A  
Boston, MA 02210  
ATTN: Privacy  

_Last Updated: 05/22/2018_
